What's up, you guys? It's Layla Lynn,
and I'm back with a new video. And in
this video, I want to talk about Amanda
Seales questioning why people are upset
and focus on Cheyenne Bryant allegedly
lying about having a doctorate degree.
And I have to say, I thought Amanda
Seales was someone who valued education.
I thought education was important to
her. I thought honesty and transparency
was important to her. Like she seems to
be a very uh
honest type of person, even if she's
saying too much. She seems to be an
honest type of person. But for whatever
reason, she is questioning why people
are upset that Dr. Cheyenne Bryant lied
about having a doctorate degree. And she
says people should be focused instead on
Kamala Harris. So we're going to get
into that in this video. But first, if
you're watching, if you haven't yet
subscribed to this channel, go ahead and
subscribe to this channel and my crime
channel, Crime in Context with Layla
Lynn.
All right, you guys. So this is what
Amanda Seales had to say about it on her
livestream.
>> Why are you all so obsessed about
Cheyenne Bryant? I'm beginning to think
that this is a bot thing.
Why are you so obsessed about this?
Like okay, she lied.
I could see if she lied and like harmed
people.
But she was on my podcast and she was
brilliant.
>> See, and this is problem number one. We
don't know if she harmed people because
there is no board that governs what
she's doing. So there's no like
process for that. So we don't know if we
if she harmed people or not. And she did
more than just podcast. I know in The
Breakfast Club, I believe it was, she
said, "Oh, well, all my work has been
public." But if you look at her website,
it says she does one-on-one and group
calls. So it's not just public. It
basically specifies that she does
private consultations. and we don't know
if she's harmed people in those
consultations with her advice.
>> I think it's enough that she lied.
You know, and then that's that. The the
the need to
If y'all went this hard against like
Kamala Harris for supporting a genocide,
then like
what would
That That would matter to me.
I don't I don't have to
>> I don't know what Kamala Harris has to
do with this. And, you know, for a lot
of people, this is why I say be careful
people who try to distract you. If we're
talking about one thing, if we're
talking about Cheyenne Bryant, there's
no need to bring Kamala Harris into it
and say, "Oh, people should be focused
on Kamala instead." That's so
unnecessary, and it's a distraction. And
normally when people are trying to
distract you, it's for a reason.
It's for a reason, and it's normally not
good.
>> There's no match. I don't need to have
some type of debate with Dr. Cheyenne
with Cheyenne Bryant. At the end of the
day, for some reason, she felt like she
needed to lie about credentials.
>> And in my opinion, I believe she lied
about credentials to have a false sense
of authority. And with authority, you
can charge more for your services. You
can go further in life, and it seems she
wanted some sort of clout, like she
talked about wanting a TV show. If you
haven't watched my previous videos on
her, make sure you watch them. But, she
talked years ago about wanting a TV
show, which requires like notoriety,
celebrity, clout. So, she lied because
she wanted clout, and you can see the
prices for her one-on-one and her group
consultations are high. They're
comparatively high, but people pay those
type of prices when they think they're
talking to a doctor. When people think
they're talking to someone that knows
better than them, they'll pay a higher
price point.
So, that's why. And I feel like Amanda
Seales
should know that.
>> I don't know why.
I think part of the reason is because we
live in a a world where we act like
credentials is what determines
somebody's effectiveness across the
board. And in some respects, it is
absolutely necessary. And in her
respect, it actually wasn't necessary
for her to do the work that she does.
That being said,
>> See, I think Amanda Seales believes when
when Cheyenne Bryant said, "Oh, all my
work has been public." I think Amanda
Seales believes her.
And maybe that's why she has the opinion
she has.
But according to her website, she does
work privately with clients. And that is
the biggest problem. If she was just a
podcast speaker speaker calling herself
a doctor like Dr. Dre, you know, a
producer calling himself a doctor,
it would be somewhat different. But to
me, the fact that she does private
one-on-one
sessions with people in session with Dr.
Bryant, it's it's problematic.
>> I just don't care.
I don't care.
She was on my podcast and she was
incredible. I don't care.
>> Because she's a speaker. She puts on
quite a show. So of course she did
incredible on a podcast.
But she hasn't learned the tools to do
like one-on-one counseling. It's not
just about the authority and the degree,
it's about having the tools and the
skill set to do the one-on-one
counseling.
>> I think it sucks and I think it was not
smart and I think that at the end of the
day, there are people who work really
hard to get doctorates. There are also
people who call themselves doctor when
they get an honorary doctorate and I
don't think that's much different.
>> I think there is a difference. It might
not be much of a difference, but I think
there is a difference. Because a
a body that's able to grant doctor
degrees honoring someone with an
honorary doctorate is still a doctorate.
Even though it's honorary, it's it's
given to them. But in her case, it seems
that nothing was awarded to her at all.
>> I don't think it's much different.
Maya Angelou was walking around calling
herself Dr. Maya Angelou. She didn't
complete a doctorate.
Some university gave her a doctorate.
What university was it? Was it Spelman?
I think it was Spelman.
>> They gave her a doctorate based on her
life's work.
They felt like her life's work was
equivalent to a doctorate degree. Now, I
know there are universities out here now
that or are like profitable like
for-profit universities that also give
people honorary doctorate degrees, which
is really like paper. It means nothing.
But as far as Dr. Maya Angelou in
particular,
she was granted that for her life's
work.
>> So, I just don't
Yeah, Maya Angelou had an honorary
doctorate. She didn't complete a
doctoral
She didn't
do doctoral study.
It's like faux faux rage
to be like all up in arms about this one
person. So, someone here said, "This one
person is influencing vulnerable black
people and therefore they are causing
harm." It's funny how you can
hand wave that away so callously. How is
she causing harm?
>> I don't think Amanda Seales realizes
that she does one-on-one counseling. I
don't think she knows all of what she is
addressing. I don't think she knows what
she's talking about.
>> How is she causing harm?
Is she giving bad advice?
Is she invoking folks to harm
themselves?
How is she causing harm?
She is falsely
using a title
to get people to to to endear people to
trust her more.
That's what?
CAUSING HARM?
I don't know, but yeah. I think I think
your your version of harm
is really loose compared to how much
harm is being caused to black people in
real life.
Listen to who you want to don't listen.
Okay?
Like I said,
Sham Bryant was on my podcast
and she was excellent.
>> I I am so surprised at this. I really
thought Amanda Seales was an intelligent
person.
But to have such a narrow perspective,
it seems like her perspective is well,
she was on my podcast and she did great.
Like that is so narrow. That is such a
narrow perspective. It's not taking into
account the other things that she's
actually done outside of podcast. It's
such a narrow perspective and I would
think Amanda Seales would think more
broadly.
>> She helped a lot of people that day.
I still get I was Even before this
happened, people would hit me and say I
really loved that episode. I learned a
lot from that episode.
I don't know why she felt she needed to
lie.
I don't and I think that that's
something she should talk to her
therapist about because I'm sure that
there's actually something very legit at
the root of that. But ultimately,
um
she's empowering people She was
empowering people. Every everything I've
seen with her has been her empowering
people.
>> This is what I mean by a narrow
perspective. For Amanda to say, "Well,
everything I've seen her say was
empowering." But you haven't heard
everything she's ever said to her
clients. You just haven't heard it. You
only know what you've seen her say on
podcast.
And that's a very
That's That's not all of her work.
>> And saying to faces they needed to hear
that
weren't trying to hear it.
>> Now,
I got to agree with that. She did tell
Cam Newton he might be considered high
value cuz he has a high income, but he
is low functioning. Same with Nick
Cannon, he's low functioning because he
cannot be emotionally there
for a dozen kids in half a dozen
households. Same with Cam Newton,
however many kids he has and however
many separate households he has,
he can provide financially, but he's not
there for them emotionally because it's
too many households. So, that is the
only part I agree with her on. The rest
of her opinion is so narrow to me. It
sounds like they made friends, so she's
defending her friend. But sometimes when
you defend people, you mess up your own
reputation.
And so, speaking of Shyanne Bryant, I
also want to share with you guys she has
started replying to people in her
comments. I do follow her page just to
see what's going on and in the past I
noticed that she wasn't really replying
and then she slowly started reposting
stories kind of making fun of herself
and now she's replying to comments.
She's also posted herself in her bikini.
I'm probably going to have to blur this
out because I had an issue on YouTube
with this before.
But this person said, "Looking very
closely, I think I actually do see a
degree."
And she said, "Multiple degrees, okay?
Get into it. Someone else said body is
PhD and she replied to them. So, she's
getting some positive comments, but
other people are still questioning her
degrees. Like this person who said did
they ever find your degrees? And she
said waiting for you smart license folks
to find them.
Someone else said not talking, but still
trying to find that dissertation. And
she said y'all so damn smart and
licensed, find the damn thing. And
someone else said body is cool, but that
can fade. However, credentials last
forever even in passing. Body is tea
though. And she said thank God I got
both as in credentials and body. So,
she's still claiming that she has these
multiple degrees with a PhD. Y'all leave
a comment, let me know what y'all think.
Is it a mental illness that she's
suffering from? What do y'all think?
Leave a comment, share your thoughts. As
always, thanks for watching.
>> Layla, Layla, Layla
Layla, Layla,
Layla tells it all.
Layla,
Layla, Layla,
Layla tells it all.
But
Layla